<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string name="physical0"> Each day people using this app have on average 30 minutes of aerobic exercise per day. </string>
<string name="physical1">Exercise helps strengthen bones, build muscle and reduce body fat.  </string>
<string name="physical2">You build lean muscle mass by working out. Even when you are sitting while lifting weights, you burn calories. </string>
<string name="physical3">Exercise makes your heart stronger, which helps it pump more blood with each heartbeat. </string>
<string name="physical4">Active people have a stronger heart. More oxygen is delivered to their body, which helps it function more efficiently. </string>
<string name="physical5">Exercise can lower blood pressure. This reduces your risk of heart disease. </string>
<string name="physical6">People who are active have reduced levels of bad cholesterol, which can clog the arteries and cause heart attacks. </string>
<string name="physical7">Exercise increases good cholesterol levels (HDL). This helps fatty deposits to be carried out of arteries. </string>
<string name="physical8">Exercise increases insulin sensitivity and prevents Type II Diabetes. </string>
<string name="physical9">Try to get at least 30 minutes of aerobic activity, 4 times per week. Being physically active can be done a little bit everyday. </string>
<string name="physical10">Try to keep a medium intensity level of activity throughout a day. Make it part of everything you do, e.g., walk briskly. </string>
<string name="physical11">You can become more active by adding even a small amount of activity into your daily routine. </string>
<string name="physical12">Time for the gym? See if you can schedule that now. </string>
<string name="physical13">Studies have shown that exercise increases blood flow to the brain. </string>
<string name="physical14">Do you have time for a walk today? Take a look at your schedule. </string>
<string name="physical15">You can go for a walk during a coffee break or during lunch. </string>
<string name="physical16">Try taking the stairs rather than elevators.  </string>
<string name="physical17">Try parking your car farther from work and take a nice walk before and after work. </string>
<string name="physical18">Chronic diseases such as heart disease and osteoporosis can be controlled through physical activity. </string>
<string name="physical19">High blood pressure can be dramatically reduced if you develop a routine of exercising on a regular basis. </string>
<string name="physical20">Hiking is a great way of both getting fit and experiencing nature. </string>
<string name="physical21">Can you walk, cycle or run today?  </string>
<string name="physical22">Walk to lunch today. Every little bit helps. </string>
<string name="physical23">Being physically active can lower your risk of several types of cancer, including colorectal cancer and breast cancer. </string>
<string name="physical24">Regular physical activity helps reduce tiredness and stress. </string>
<string name="physical25">Exercise helps improve self-esteem, and increases heart and muscle strength. </string>
<string name="physical26">Regular exercise helps you burn calories faster because exercise builds lean muscle (which burns more calories than fat). </string>
<string name="physical27">Exercise can be fun if you have a workout buddy. Reach out and find one.</string>
<string name="physical28">To raise your heart rate during your regular day you can take the stairs instead of the elevator. </string>
<string name="physical29">When combined with a healthy diet, exercise can speed up weight loss. </string>
<string name="physical30">Kickstart your metabolism during your regular day by turning off the TV/Internet and take the dog for a walk. </string>
<string name="physical31">Burn more calories during your regular day by biking to work, or park further away from your office so you have to walk further. </string>
<string name="physical32">You\'ll feel better and keep your weight under control if you exercise regularly - and eat less. </string>
<string name="physical33">Exercise combined with a healthy diet speeds up weight loss. </string>
<string name="physical34">Being active reduces your risk of cancer. </string>
<string name="physical35">Regular physical activity helps reduce tiredness and stress.  </string>
<string name="physical36">Exercise releases naturally energizing endorphins. You feel better about yourself when you exercise. </string>
<string name="physical37"> Controlling your weight is easier when you are active. </string>
<string name="physical38">Join a friend on a walk or run. </string>
<string name="physical39">Give into positive peer pressure. </string>
<string name="physical40">Did you know your friends are physically active? </string>
<string name="physical41">Use the stairs and catch up. </string>
<string name="physical42">Develop an exercise routine.  </string>
<string name="physical43">Join an exercise class – there is Yoga, Zumba... </string>
</resources>