<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string name="sleep0">Each day, people using this app sleep around 8.5 hours. </string>
<string name="sleep1">Relaxation techniques, such as meditation and yoga, can help you relax before bed. </string>
<string name="sleep2">Read a few pages of a good book in bed at night - then hit the snooze button. </string>
<string name="sleep3">Don’t bring your laptop to bed. </string>
<string name="sleep4">Avoid TV before bed. </string>
<string name="sleep5">Reading or doing a crossword puzzle will send you to sleep ;-) </string>
<string name="sleep6">Exercise regularly, but don\'t exercise within a few hours before going to bed. </string>
<string name="sleep7">If you feel stressed or tied during the day, you likely need more sleep. </string>
<string name="sleep8">People who are often sleep deprived have been shown to be at greater risk of heart disease. </string>
<string name="sleep9">Too little sleep (less that 8 hours) and too much sleep is unhealthy for you.  </string>
<string name="sleep10">Individuals that do not have enough sleep are more likely to get diabetes. </string>
<string name="sleep11">Poor sleep is associated with depression, anxiety, memory impairment and weight gain. </string>
<string name="sleep12">Insufficient sleep has been shown to lead to reduced immune system functioning and heart conditions. </string>
<string name="sleep13">Studies show that men and women who do not get enough sleep have more car accidents. </string>
<string name="sleep14">Sleep habits are known to be important in achieving high quality sleep. Go to sleep and wake up and a scheduled time. </string>
<string name="sleep15">Studies show that we should be regular with the times we sleep and wake up even if sometimes you sleep only a few hours. </string>
<string name="sleep16">Research shows bedrooms should be quiet and dark. If noise is a problem, use a fan to mask the noise or use earplugs. </string>
<string name="sleep17">If you do not get enough sleep on a regular basis, you are at increased risk of diseases such as high blood pressure. </string>
<string name="sleep18">Taking a hot bath and massaging your legs before bedtime helps you relax. </string>
<string name="sleep19">Try and have an early night tonight. </string>
<string name="sleep20">Tired? Get to bed early. </string>
<string name="sleep21">Enjoy listening to classical music? It can also be a great way to relax before falling asleep. </string>
<string name="sleep22">Do not lie in bed worrying about things. Set aside another to think about your challenges such as after dinner or during your shower or bathroom break. </string>
<string name="sleep23">If you can go to bed at the same time each night, try and get a sufficient amount of sleep every night. </string>
<string name="sleep24">Do the same thing every night before going to sleep. One example, take a warm bath and read for 10 minutes every night.  </string>
<string name="sleep25">Developing a bedtime routine will help you reach or exceed this number </string>
<string name="sleep26">Individuals lacking sleep are more likely to get diabetes. </string>
<string name="sleep27">Without enough sleep you are more like to have car accidents. </string>
<string name="sleep28">Difficult day at work today? Call it an early night. </string>
<string name="sleep29">When you have enough sleep it\'s easier in dealing with stress. </string>
<string name="sleep30">Even if you are busy you need sleep to remain productive. </string>
<string name="sleep31">Others find time to sleep, you should too; it is important! </string>
<string name="sleep32">You can\'t make good decisions without enough sleep. </string>
<string name="sleep33">Sleep gives you energy. </string>
<string name="sleep34">Avoid feeling stress or blue by getting enough sleep. </string>
<string name="sleep35">You deserve to sleep too!. </string>
<string name="sleep36">Sleep is not an optional activity, just look at your peers. </string>
<string name="sleep37">"Go to sleep early to wake up on time. Let a good night’s sleep grow you mind, body and soul and let it give you inner peace."    ~Hindi Proverb </string>
</resources>
