<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string name="social0">Each day people using this app have on average five unique personal interactions each lasting about 15-30 minutes. </string>
<string name="social1">How about going to the movies with your friends. </string>
<string name="social2">Talk to friend today. </string>
<string name="social3">Social activities reduce stress. </string>
<string name="social4">Being social decreases the risk of feeling blue. </string>
<string name="social5">Missed a friend’s birthday? Call and wish the a belated happy birthday. </string>
<string name="social6">Check Facebook and talk to a friend about to have a birthday. </string>
<string name="social7">Volunteer with a group of friends or co-workers. </string>
<string name="social8">We all feel too busy to talk to friends, but try today. </string>
<string name="social9">Being around family and friends you enjoy can help reduce stress. </string>
<string name="social10">Hop online and look for fun activities near you to get involved. </string>
<string name="social11">Being sociable lowers stress. </string>
<string name="social12">How about watching sports with your friends or family. </string>
<string name="social13">Any good cafes near you that you like? Drop by. </string>
<string name="social14">Check out a new café with a friend. </string>
<string name="social15">To get more out of your relationships, you can ask for specific kinds of help. Even a best friend can’t read your mind. </string>
<string name="social16">Taking part in social events, sports and hobbies can help you deal with stress. </string>
<string name="social17">Show how much you respect, support and appreciate your friends and family. They may not realize you do. </string>
<string name="social18">You may think positive thoughts, but sharing them works wonders. </string>
<string name="social19">Research tells us people should move out of relationships that make them feel unsafe or lead to lower self-esteem. </string>
<string name="social20">Being social has been shown to increase lifespan. </string>
<string name="social21">Shyness and anxiety can prevent one from making friends. Try to step out of your comfort zone and meet others. </string>
<string name="social22">No time to keep in touch? Add a reminder to your calendar to connect to people you care about. </string>
<string name="social23">If you want to get more out of your relationships make a list of the people you want to contact regularly. </string>
<string name="social24">Have real quality time! Commit to spending time with people without phones, computers, ipods or other distracting devices. </string>
<string name="social25">Life is full of interruptions and distractions. Take some time out with people you love to hang with. </string>
<string name="social26">Relationships that draw people into unhealthy habits like abusing drugs, have been shown to hurt those involved. </string>
<string name="social27">Have fun, do something social tonight. </string>
<string name="social28">Being on Facebook is cool but nothing beats face-to-face conservations with friends. </string>
<string name="social29">Being social can improve your health. </string>
<string name="social30">Social connections increase happiness. In one study, a key difference between happy and unhappy people were relationships. </string>
<string name="social31">Movie tonight? </string>
<string name="social32">Tired of the routine? Invite your neighbors over for dinner. </string>
<string name="social33">Early dinner? </string>
<string name="social34">Call a friend. </string>
<string name="social35">Reach out to a friend you haven’t spoken to in decades. </string>
<string name="social36">Check out a park.  </string>
<string name="social37">Join a social club. </string>
<string name="social38">Keep appointments. </string>
<string name="social39">Circulate. </string>
<string name="social40">Deep, relaxed breathing may help relieve stress. Oxygen is the body\'s antidote to stress. </string>
<string name="social41">Relax with a friend. </string>
<string name="social42">Music tonight? </string>
<string name="social43">Your social score could be better, try contact a friend. </string>
<string name="social44">What makes you feel good socially? Do it! </string>
<string name="social45">Stressful day? Take a break and do something fun </string>
</resources>